(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
燦鳥ノム presents ウィンター mini ライブ
Suntory Nomu presents Winter Mini Live
2月25日 21:00～ Start!!
Starting at 21:00 on February 25th!!
冷蔵庫から、こんばんは！
Good evening from the refrigerator!
あ、
Ah,
水のように清らかに
Pure like water,
太陽のようにみんなを照らす
shining on everyone like the sun,
サントリー公式バーチャルYouTuberの
Suntory's official Virtual YouTuber,
燦鳥ノムです！
Suntory Nom!
燦鳥ノム
Suntory Nom
はーい！
Hi!
本日はサントリーノムプレゼンツ、ウィンターミニライブということで
Today is Suntory Nom Presents, Winter Mini Live,
素敵なゲストの方々が来ております！
and some wonderful guests are here!
それでは、まずそらちゃんから自己紹介をお願いいたします！
So first, Sora-chan, please introduce yourself!
はーい！
Hi!
皆さん、こんにちは！ときのそらです！
Hello everyone! I'm Tokino Sora!
本日はこんな素敵なライブにゲスト出演させていただいて、とっても嬉しいなって思っています。
I'm very happy to be a guest performer at such a wonderful live today.
ときのそら
Tokino Sora
本日はどうぞよろしくお願いいたします！
Thank you for having me!
よろしくお願いします！
Nice to meet you!
さあ、続いて初めましてのラミィちゃん、お願いいたします！
Now next, Lamy-chan, who I'm meeting for the first time, please go ahead!
はーい！
Hi!
初めまして！こんらみー！
Nice to meet you! Kon-Lamy!
ホロライブの雪花ラミィと申します！
I'm Yukihana Lamy from Hololive!
雪花ラミィ
Yukihana Lamy
や、もう今すごい緊張してるんですけど
I'm really nervous right now,
今日は楽しんでいこうと思いますので、よろしくお願いします！
but I'm going to have fun today, so please treat me well!
よろしくお願いします！
Nice to meet you!
やー、ラミィちゃん、初めましてなんですが、さっそく
Wow, Lamy-chan, it's our first time meeting... but can I
「ラミィちゃん」とお呼びしてよろしいでしょうか？
call you "Lamy-chan" right away?
もちろんですよ！
Of course!
ノムちゃんって呼んでもいいですか？
Can I call you Nom-chan?
もちろんです！
Of course!
ノムちゃん、よろしくお願いします！
Nom-chan, nice to meet you!
よろしくお願いします！
Nice to meet you!
はい、やー、本日は素敵な御二人と楽しんでライブをしてまいります。
Yes, well, today I'll be enjoying the live with these two wonderful ladies.
そらちゃんとは以前にも「歌ってみた」を一緒に歌わせていただいたり
I've collaborated with Sora-chan before on "Utattemita" videos,
色々とご一緒させていただく機会があったんですが
and have had many opportunities to work together,
本日のライブの意気込みをお伺いしてよろしいでしょうか？
but may I ask about your enthusiasm for today's live?
はーい！もうお久しぶりにね、ノムちゃんと一緒に
Hi! It's been a while since I've been with Nom-chan,
そしてね、後輩のラミィちゃんと一緒にライブに立てるということで
and now I'm on stage with my junior Lamy-chan,
今日はね、テンションが高まっています！
so I'm really pumped up today!
なので、なんか皆に素敵な音楽をプレゼントできるように
So, to be able to give everyone some wonderful music,
そして楽しいミニライブになるように頑張ります！よろしくお願いします！
and to make it a fun mini live, I'll do my best! Thank you!
よろしくお願いします！ありがとうございます！
Nice to meet you! Thank you very much!
さあ、ラミィちゃん。ラミィちゃんも本当に本日のライブに本当にぴったりということで
Now, Lamy-chan. Lamy-chan is really a perfect fit for today's live,
今回お招きできて光栄なんですが、ラミィちゃんの意気込みをお伺いしてよろしいでしょうか？
so I'm honored to have you. Could you tell us about your enthusiasm?
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
はい！今日はね、もう本当にさっきも言ったんですけど
Yes! Today, as I said before,
ライブ、ミニライブに参加させていただいて今本当にもうドキドキがすごいんですけど
participating in this live, mini live, my heart is really racing right now,
そら先輩と、ノムちゃんと、いっぱい笑顔で楽しんでいきたいと思います！
but I want to have lots of fun with Sora-senpai and Nom-chan with a big smile!
頑張ります！
I'll do my best!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
はい！本日は三人で素敵なライブをお届けしたいと思います！
Yes! Today the three of us will bring you a wonderful live!
えー、一つですね、お詫びと訂正がございまして
Umm, I have one apology and correction to make.
燦鳥ノムのTwitterにて、あのハッシュタグが「そらゆきノムライブ」と
On Suntory Nom's Twitter, the hashtag was listed as "#SoraYukiNomLive",
記載されていたんですが
but once again,
改めまして、あのライブの感想などはぜひハッシュタグ「#ノムlive」にてお願いいたします！
please use the hashtag "#NomLive" for your impressions of the live!
よろしくお願いします！
Thank you!
はい、あ、たくさんコメントも来ておりますね！ありがとうございます！
Yes, oh, lots of comments are coming in! Thank you very much!
はい！それでは早速なんですけれども
Yes! Well then, without further ado,
私からトップバッターを切らせていただきたいと思います！
I'll be the first one to start!
そらちゃん、ラミィちゃんの素敵なお歌も続きますので
Sora-chan and Lamy-chan's wonderful songs will follow,
本日は最後までお楽しみください！
so please enjoy until the end!
それでは、ステージとマイクのセッティングに少しお時間をいただきますので
Now, we'll need a little time to set up the stage and microphone,
皆様、少々お待ちください！
so everyone, please wait a moment!
バイバーイ！
Bye-bye!
ただいまセッティング中です　しばらくお待ちください
Currently setting up. Please wait for a while.
こんなに まぶしい季節は
Such a bright season,
いつのまにか
Before I even realized it
人混みに紛れても
Even if I'm lost in a crowd
同じ空見てるのに
Though we're looking at the same sky
風に吹かれて
Blown by the wind
僕は君の全てなど
I don't know everything about you
知ってはいないだろう
and I probably never will
それでも一億人から
But out of a hundred million people
君を見つけたよ
I'm the one who found you
根拠はないけど 本気で思ってるんだ
I have no proof, but I truly believe it from my heart
些細な言い合いもなくて
Without even minor arguments
ララライ ララライ
La-la-la, la-la-la
同じ時間を生きてなどいけない
We can't live through the same time
素直になれないなら
If we can't be honest with ourselves
喜びも悲しみも
Both joy and sadness
虚しいだけ
will just be empty
粉雪ねえ 心まで白く
Powder snow, hey, if only my heart
染められたなら
could be dyed white
二人の孤独を分け合う
Sharing the loneliness of two
ことが出来たのかい
Was I able to do that?
僕は君の心に
I want to press my ear
耳を押し当てて
right against your heart
その声のする方へ
Toward the direction of that voice
すーっと深く深く降りていきたい
I want to descend forever deeper
そこでもう一度会おう
Let's meet there once again
分かり合いたいなんて
Thinking we want to understand each other
ララライ ララライ
La-la-la, la-la-la
上辺をなでていたのは僕の方
I was the one just brushing the surface
君のかじかんだ手も
Even your frozen hands
握りしめることだけで
just by gripping them tightly
繋がってたのに
we were connected
粉雪ねえ 永遠を前に
Powder snow, hey, before eternity
あまりに脆く
it's so very fragile
ざらつくアスファルトの上
On top of the rough asphalt
シミになってゆくよ
it turns into a stain
粉雪ねえ 時に頼りなく
Powder snow, hey, sometimes unreliably
心は揺れる
my heart wavers
それでも僕は君のこと
Even so, I want to keep
守り続けたい
protecting you
粉雪ねえ 心まで白く
Powder snow, hey, if only my heart
染められたなら
could be dyed white
二人の孤独を包んで
Wrapping the loneliness of two
空に返すから
and returning it to the sky
鏡よ鏡よ鏡さん 世界で一番可愛くなるのは
Mirror, mirror, mirror on the wall, to become the most beautiful in the world—
やめてよ 棘のような視線迫る
Stop it, those thorn-like gazes are closing in.
優しいふりした彼女が 素敵な晩餐もてなした
She, who pretended to be kind, served a wonderful dinner.
そっと口に含むと
As I gently take a bite...
嗚呼 薄れゆく 意識の中で
Ah... within my fading consciousness...
夢を見てる いつかのお伽話 時が止まる
I'm dreaming. Like an old fairy tale, time stands still.
お願いキスで 目を覚ましてほしいの
Please, I want you to wake me up with a kiss.
白い棺から 連れ出すように
As if to take me away from the white coffin.
突き刺さる憎しみは ドラマティックな地上を
The piercing hatred traverses the dramatic earth.
祈っても君はまだ来ない
Even if I pray, you still don't come.
嗚呼
Ah...
鏡よ鏡よ鏡さん ネクタイ任せや頬にアイサツするから
Mirror, mirror, mirror on the wall, since I'll leave the tie to you and greet your cheek...
妬みも変わってしまった
Even the jealousy has changed.
7人の小人はいるけれど 助ける素振り知らんぷりね
The seven dwarves are there, but they feign ignorance of any attempt to help.
そっと首を掴まれ
With my neck gently grasped...
嗚呼 一粒の 涙さえも
Ah... even a single tear...
拭えなくて 呼吸もままならない 世界捨てた
I couldn't wipe it away, I could hardly breathe, I threw away the world.
凍えそうだから 早く駆けてほしいの
I'm about to freeze, so I want you to run to me quickly.
理由は聞かないで 答えられない
Don't ask why, I can't answer.
望まない憎まれは 深い愛の地上を
Unwanted resentment traverses the earth of deep love.
もうすぐでいなくなるのかな
I wonder if I'll be gone soon.
途切れてゆく 命の音
The sound of life is fading away.
毒リンゴを 食した少女のように 眠りにつく
Falling asleep like the girl who ate the poisoned apple.
お願いキスで 目を覚ましてほしいの
Please, I want you to wake me up with a kiss.
胸の奥の声 届きますか
Does the voice from the depth of my heart reach you?
階段を登ったら ドアを開けるだけで
If you climb the stairs, just by opening the door...
見つかるよ 嗚呼
I'll be found. Ah...
お願いキスで 目を覚ましてほしいの
Please, I want you to wake me up with a kiss.
白い棺から 連れ出すように
As if to take me away from the white coffin.
突き刺さる憎しみは ドラマティックな地上を
The piercing hatred traverses the dramatic earth.
祈っても君はまだ来ない
Even if I pray, you still don't come.
嗚呼 消えてしまう
Ah... I'm going to disappear...
その前に
Before that happens.
くるりくるりよ
Spinning round and round—
アップスアンドダウンズ
Ups and downs.
雪と愛が 世界を救う
Snow and love will save the world
絶対いつか 出会えるはずなの
I'm sure we'll meet someday
沈む夕日に 淋しく一人
Alone and lonely in the setting sun
拳握りしめる 私
I clench my fists
週休二日 しかもフレックス
Two days off a week and flexible hours too
相手はどこにでも いるんだから
My partner could be anywhere
今夜飲み会 期待している
I'm looking forward to tonight's drinking party
友達の友達に
With a friend of a friend
目立つにはどうしたら いいの
What should I do to stand out?
一番の悩み
That's my biggest worry
性格良ければいい
If your personality is good, that's enough
そんなの嘘だと 思いませんか？
Don't you think that's a lie?
Boy meets girl 幸せの予感
Boy meets girl, a premonition of happiness
きっと誰かを 感じてる
I'm sure I'm feeling someone
Fall in love ロマンスの神様
Fall in love, god of romance
この人でしょうか
Is this the person?
ノリと恥じらい 必要なのよ
Enthusiasm and bashfulness are necessary
初対面の 男の人って
When meeting a man for the first time
年齢 住所 趣味に職業
Age, address, hobbies, and occupation
さりげなくチェック しなくちゃ
I have to check them subtly
待ていますか 合格ライン
Are you waiting? The passing line
早くサングラス 取って見せてよ
Quickly, take off your sunglasses and show me
笑顔が素敵 真顔も素敵
A wonderful smile, a wonderful serious face
思わず見とれて しまうの
I find myself staring unintentionally
幸せになれるもの ならば
If I can be happy
友情より愛情
Then love over friendship
「帰りを送らせて」と
Asking to "delay the return home"
突然ちょっと 信じられない
Suddenly, I can't believe it
Boy meets girl 恋してる瞬間
Boy meets girl, the moment I fall in love
きっとあなたを 感じてる
I'm sure I'm feeling you
Fall in love ロマンスの神様
Fall in love, god of romance
願いをかなえて
Make my wish come true
Boy meets girl 恋する気持ち
Boy meets girl, the feeling of love
何より素敵な 宝物
The most wonderful treasure of all
Fall in love ロマンスの神様
Fall in love, god of romance
どうもありがとう
Thank you so much
よく当たる 星占いに
In the horoscope that's often right
そういえば書いてあった
Come to think of it, it was written
今日会う人と 結ばれる
I'll be tied to the person I meet today
今週も来週も 再来週もずっと
This week, next week, the week after, forever
はい！ はい！ はい！ はい！
Hoi! Hoi! Hoi! Hoi!
みんな、盛り上がってますかー？
Is everyone having a good time?
今日は最後まで 楽しんでいこうね！
Let's have fun until the very end today!
土曜日遊園地 一年たったらハネムーン
Saturday at the amusement park, a year later it's a honeymoon
Fall in love ロマンスの神様
Fall in love, god of romance
感謝しています
I'm grateful
いつまでもずっと この気持ち
This feeling forever and ever
忘れたくない
I don't want to forget
Fall in love ロマンスの神様
Fall in love, god of romance
どうもありがとう
Thank you so much
ただいまセッティング中です しばらくお待ちください
Currently setting up. Please wait a moment.
ただいまセッティング中です　しばらくお待ちください
Settings in progress. Please wait for a while.
皆さんお疲れ様でしたー！
Great job everyone!
お疲れ様でしたー！
Great job!
ありがとうございましたー！
Thank you very much!
さて、後半もまだまだライブは続きますが、その前に少し休憩いたしましょう。
Well, the live show will continue in the second half, but before that, let's take a short break.
はい！
Okay!
後ろにあのペットボトル用意させていただいておりますので、そちらのドリンクをお飲みください。
We've prepared some bottled drinks in the back, so please have a drink.
やったー！
Yay!
やったー！ ありがとうございます！
Yay! Thank you!
さあ、たくさんありますわよ。
Well, there's plenty of them.
どれにしようかな。
Which one should I choose?
いっぱい、いっぱいありますよ。
There's lots and lots of them.
私はこちら。
I'll take this one.
えーと、これ！ これにします！
Um, this one! I'll go with this!
では、乾杯いたしましょうか。
Then, shall we have a toast?
はい！
Yes!
行きますわよ、せーの！
Here we go, ready set...
乾杯ー！
Cheers!
あー、染みる。染みわたる。
Ah, it hits the spot. It really sinks in.
おおー。
Ohh.
美味しい！
Delicious!
美味しいですわね。
It's delicious, isn't it?
美味しい。
It's good.
皆様もコメントありがとうございます。
Thank you all for your comments too.
ありがとうございます。
Thank you.
皆様からの感想なども読みたいなぁと思うんですけども。
I'd love to read some of your thoughts as well.
さっきもありがとうございます、「乾杯乾杯」と。
Thanks for all the 'cheers' earlier.
はい、やっぱり嬉しいですわね。
Yes, it really makes me happy.
「もぐもぐタイム」ということで。
So it's 'munching time'.
もぐもぐタイム。ありがとうございます。
Munching time. Thank you.
さて、ウィンターミニライブまだまだ続くんですけども、実はここで皆様にお伝えしたいことがございまして。
Well, the Winter Mini Live is still going on, but there's actually something I want to tell you all.
なにか？
What is it?
先ほど飲んでいただいたドリンクなんですが、実は一人だけ違う飲み物を飲んでおります！
Regarding the drinks you just had, actually one person is drinking something different!
ええー！？
What!?
果たしてそれが誰なのか。では今から私達で推理をしていきたいなと思います。
I wonder who that is. Well, from now on, let's try to deduce it ourselves.
なんたって！ なんと！
What! No way!
題して、「違う飲み物を飲んでいるのは誰だ！？ドリンクウルフ！！」
Titled, 'Who's Drinking the Different Drink!? Drink Wolf!!'
イェーイ！
Yay!
今からですね一人だけ違う飲み物を飲んだ人を探し当てるのですが。
Now, we're going to find out the one person who drank something different.
単に会話をしながらですとちょっと簡単なので。
But just talking normally would be a bit too easy.
今回はですね、カードで引いた生き物の語尾をつけて挑戦していただきたいなと思います！
So this time, I want you to challenge it using the sentence ending of a creature drawn from a card!
なるほど！
I see!
では、カード、その語尾のカード、そらちゃんにでは引いていただきましょう。
Now, the card, let's have Sora-chan draw the sentence-ending card.
そらちゃんお願いいたします。
Sora-chan, if you please.
なんの語尾があるんでしょうね？
I wonder what kind of sentence endings there are?
どんな語尾か楽しみですわね。
I'm looking forward to seeing what it is.
さあ、そらちゃん、カードの発表お願いいたします。
Now, Sora-chan, please announce the card.
ネコ！
Cat!
あ、猫ちゃん！ 可愛らしい。
Oh, a kitty! How cute.
猫ちゃんの語尾は、「にゃん」！
A kitty's sentence ending is, 'nyan'!
にゃん！
Nyan!
そうだにゃん。
That's right, nyan.
そうだにゃんだよ。
にゃん。
Nyan.
にゃんですわね。
Nyan, isn't it?
はい、さあ。どなたがじゃあ、あ、もう始めてよろしいんでしょうか？
Okay, then. Well, shall we start already?
よろしいにゃん。
Ready, nyan.
よろしいにゃん。ではあの語尾はにゃんでいきましょう。
Ready, nyan. Then let's go with 'nyan' for the ending.
はーいにゃん！
Okay, nyan!
それでは皆様、どなたが違う飲み物を飲んでいるのでしょうか？ということで。
Well then everyone, who do you think is drinking the different drink?
シンキングタイム、スタート！
Thinking time, start!
イェーイ！ スタートだにゃん！
Yay! Starting, nyan!
ちなみに、どんなお味でした？
By the way, what was the taste like?
お味にゃん？
The taste, nyan?
お味にゃんにゃん？
The taste, nyan nyan?
お味にゃん...ええと、さっぱりしてたにゃん。
The taste nyan... Um, it was refreshing, nyan.
さわやかだったにゃん。
It was clean, nyan.
ラミィが飲んだのもさわやかだったにゃんね？
Lamy's drink was clean too, right nyan?
はーい！
Yes!
そらちゃんは、しゅわっとしたかにゃん？
Sora-chan, was yours fizzy, nyan?
しゅわっとしたかにゃん。
Was it fizzy, nyan?
そういう聞き方ありにゃん？
Is that kind of question allowed, nyan?
なしかにゃん？
Is it not, nyan?
ちなみにしゅわっとしたかにゃん？
By the way, was it fizzy, nyan?
せーの！
Ready, set...
カンパーイ！
Cheers!
みんな知ってるにゃんね。
Everyone knows, right?
どんな時に飲みたいにゃん？
When do you want to drink it?
あー、いい質問だにゃん。
Ah, that's a good question.
それはどんな時...うーん...
When would that be... hmm...
スカッとしたい時かにゃん？
When you want to feel refreshed?
スカッとしたい時にゃんか。
スカッとしたい時。あ、でも...
When I want to feel refreshed. Ah, but...
わかるにゃ。ラミィも結構スカッとした時に飲みたいにゃんね。
I get it. Lamy also wants to drink it when she's refreshed.
あー、こう、なんか目を覚ましたい時とか...
Ah, like, when you want to wake up...
あー、飲みたいにゃんね。
Ah, you'd want to drink then.
そらちゃんは違う時かにゃん？
Is it different for Sora-chan?
いや、でも、どっちかって言うと...
No, but, if I had to say...
どうしましょう。わたくしが...どんな時かにゃん？
What should I do? I... when would it be?
そらちゃんはどんな時かにゃん？
When is it for Sora-chan?
私はお風呂とか温かいとこ行った後とかにさっぱり飲みたいにゃん。
I want to drink it refreshing after a bath or being somewhere warm.
そしたらラミィと違うかにゃ？
Then, is it different from Lamy?
いや、えーっ！？
No, what!?
いや、ラミィは、やっぱりあーっ、スッキリしたい時...あれ？
No, Lamy is, after all, when I want to feel refreshed... wait?
あれれ？あれれれ？
Wait, what? Wait a minute...
ラミィにゃにゃにゃ？
Lamy-nyanyanya?
あれ？にゃにゃにゃ？
Wait? Nyanyanya?
終わってしまいました。はい終了ですわ。
It's over. Yes, it's finished.
終了ですにゃ。
It's finished.
えーっ！にゃんにゃー！
What! Nyan-nya!
皆さんどうでしたか？ね。
How was it for everyone? Right.
わたくしなんだか、そらちゃんと同じようにゃ。
Somehow, I feel the same as Sora-chan.
本当、にゃん？
Really?
そらちゃんと同じようにゃ。
The same as Sora-chan.
なんか、え、みんなしたにゃん？
Like, eh, everyone did it?
みんな一緒に感じてしまったにゃんな。
We all felt it together, didn't we?
全員同じ！
Everyone is the same!
全員！でもそんなことないにゃん。
Everyone! But that can't be.
誰か一人は違うにゃん。
Someone must be different.
うーん、どっちかにゃ。
Hmm, which one could it be?
わたくし、そうですね...えっ、何ですか？
For me, well... eh, what is it?
天の声、なんか...
The voice from above, something...
天の声がどうしたにゃ、どうしたにゃん？
What happened to the voice from above?
どうしたにゃ？
What's wrong?
位置を変わってくださいと言われました。
I was told to change positions.
わたくしだけ違うとかそんな...そんなことですか？
Is it because only I'm different? Is that it?
あれ？あれ？もしかして天の声が助言したにゃ？
Wait, wait. Did the voice from above give advice?
ほーにゃ！ほーにゃ！
Oh, nyan! Oh, nyan!
あなから落ちるとかそんなのないですよ。
There's no falling through a hole or anything like that.
困りましたわ。何も聞いてないにゃん。
I'm in trouble. I haven't heard anything.
そんなの聞いてなかったにゃん。ええーっ！
I hadn't heard about that. What!
これは多分...いや、も...
This is probably... no, even...
じゃあ、じゃあラミィちゃん...これは天の声から...
Then, then Lamy-chan... this is from the voice from above...
ノムちゃんが場所移動言われたにゃんの？
Nomu-chan was told to move?
ええー、わたくしでしょうか？
Eh, is it me?
えっ、わたくしでしょうか？
ラミィちゃん、わたくし怪しいと思ってるのかにゃ？
Lamy-chan, do you think I'm suspicious?
いやもう天の声がそう言ってるにゃ。
The voice from above is already saying so.
私も天の声を信じるにゃ。
I'll believe the voice from above too.
そんなことない！
That's not true!
違いますわ。深読みです。きっと何か事情があるんですわ。
No. You're overthinking it. There must be some reason.
皆さん、コメント、どうですか？
Everyone, how are the comments?
わたくしは...わたくし、わたくしもよろしいですか？
I... can I also...?
いいのよ、いいのよ。
It's okay, it's okay.
ラミィちゃんかね、と思っていましたわ。
I thought it might be Lamy-chan.
うおー。
Whoa.
ね、コメントの皆さんいかがですか？
Right, what does everyone in the comments think?
みんな笑っているにゃ。
Everyone is laughing.
ね、いやーどうだったんでしょう。
Right, well, how was it?
それでは、あの、皆が何を飲んだのか、誰がウルフだったのか...
Well then, who drank what, and who was the wolf...
発表させていただきます。
I will announce it.
こちらです。せーの！
Here it is. Ready, set...
ドン！
Go!
燦鳥ノム 天然水スパークリングレモン
Suntory Nomu: Natural Water Sparkling Lemon
ときのそら C.C.レモン
Tokino Sora: C.C. Lemon
雪花ラミィ C.C.レモン
Yukihana Lamy: C.C. Lemon
あーっ！一人でしたわ！
Ah! It was only one person!
わたくし、そんな気がしてましたわ。この場所移動で。うーん。
I had a feeling about that. With the position change. Hmm.
あ、なるほど。ここにテロップが出ると。
Ah, I see. Captions appear here.
でもそれにしてもわたくしが違う。
But even so, I'm the one who's different.
あー、でもそんな気がしてたにゃん。
Ah, but I had a feeling.
やっぱりさっぱりしたい時にね、飲みたいにゃ。飲みたいにゃ。
As I thought, you want to drink it when you want to feel refreshed.
わたくしもでもC.C.レモン飲んだような気がしてきましたわ。
I'm starting to feel like I drank C.C. Lemon too.
天然水スパークリングレモンって出てるのに。
Even though it says Natural Water Sparkling Lemon.
確かに同じレモンでどっちも美味しいから。
True, they're both lemon and both delicious.
可笑しいですわね。ちょっとあの、もう一回お願いしたいですわ。
It's strange. I'd like to ask for one more round.
いいよ、もう一回行きましょう。
Sure, let's go again.
時間よろしいですか？もう一戦できますか？
Is there enough time? Can we do one more match?
やったー！じゃあ、もう一回行きましょう。ドン！
Yay! Then, let's go again. Bam!
ドリンクをもう一回よろしいですか？選んで。選びましょうか。
Can we choose a drink again? Choose. Let's choose.
では、わたくしから。あ、カードを引かなくて大丈夫かにゃ？
Then, from me. Oh, is it okay not to draw a card?
あとにゃ、あとに引くにゃ。
Later, we'll draw later.
ははは。これはそらちゃんが違うんでしょうね、きっと。
Hahaha. Sora-chan is surely the different one this time.
待って、まだ誰も飲んでない。誰も選んでないにゃん。
Wait, no one has drunk yet. No one has chosen yet.
どういうことにゃ！どういうことにゃん！？
What do you mean!? What do you mean!?
どういうことにゃ？
What do you mean?
わたくしは次はそら先輩を指します。
I'll point to Sora-senpai next.
さあ、そらちゃんは何を選ぶんでしょうね、皆さん。
Now, what will Sora-chan choose, everyone?
ラミィちゃんもカード引かなくてはですね。
Lamy-chan also has to draw a card.
これを持って来たにゃん。
I brought this.
きっと違うんでしょうね。
It's probably different.
なんで！？なんで！？
Why!? Why!?
ラミィ来ます。ふふふ。
Lamy is coming. Fufu.
さあ、何でしょうね、お楽しみですね。お楽しみですね。
Well, what will it be? We're looking forward to it.
ラミィちゃん選びましたか？
Did Lamy-chan choose?
これにするにゃ。
I'll go with this.
はい。じゃあ先に乾杯を...
Yes. Then, first a toast...
どうしましょう、乾杯をしてからカードを引きます。
What should we do, we'll draw cards after the toast.
行きましょう！
Let's go!
はい！
Yes!
せーの、乾杯！
One, two, cheers!
あ、これは。飲みやすい喉越し。
Oh, this... It goes down very smoothly.
じゃあ、ラミィちゃんにカードを引いていただきましょうか。
Well then, shall we have Lamy-chan draw a card?
あ、はい、引きます。
Ah, yes, I'll draw.
じゃあ今のうちにそらちゃん、何でした？
In the meantime, Sora-chan, what was it?
言えないよ！言ったらだめだよ！ゲームにならないよ。
I can't say! You can't say it! The game will be ruined.
はい、ラミィちゃん、おかえりなさい。では、ラミィちゃん、どんな語尾か発表してください。
Okay, Lamy-chan, welcome back. Now, Lamy-chan, please announce your gobi.
はい！次の語尾は...熱血！
Yes! The next gobi is... Hot-blooded!
熱血？熱血？
Hot-blooded? Hot-blooded?
熱血の...語尾というか、これはキャラじゃないですかね。
Hot-blooded... rather than a gobi, isn't that more like a character?
熱血キャラ！熱血キャラ！
A hot-blooded character! Hot-blooded character!
行くぞー！おい！おら行くぞー！
Let's go! Hey! Whoa, here I go!
スッキリだぜ！
I'm refreshed, daze!
そうですね。ちょっと戻ってますよ。
That's right. You've reverted a bit.
戻ってますよ。何を飲んだんだ！？
You've reverted! What on earth did you drink!?
えーっと、熱血の方の一人称って何なんでしょうか。
Um, what would be the first-person pronoun for a hot-blooded person?
あ、そういうこと？えーっと、熱血になればいいんだ！
Oh, I see. Well, as long as you're hot-blooded!
そうですよ！語尾、熱血っぽければいいんですよ。
Exactly! As long as the sentence ending sounds hot-blooded.
吾輩は...
Wagahai (I) is...
スッキリ整ったなり！
I'm feeling refreshed and ready, nari!
シンキングタイムスタートします！始まったぜ！
Thinking time starts now! It's begun, daze!
始まったぜ！始まったぜ！
It's begun, daze! It's begun, daze!
どうだ？どうだぜ？
How is it? How is it, daze?
なんだ、私も同じくスッキリしたと思うぜ！
What, I also think I feel refreshed, daze!
あ、かっこいい！かっこいいぜ！
Ah, cool! That's cool, daze!
えーっと、俺もスッキリしたと思うぜ！
Um, I also think I feel refreshed, daze!
みんな一緒だ！みんな一緒だな！
Everyone's the same! Everyone is the same, huh!
じゃあだめじゃないですか。誰も当てられないぞ、それ。
Then that's no good. No one will be able to guess at this rate.
えーっと、なんかもっと特徴とか、どんな時に飲むとか、あるだろう！
Um, there must be more features, like when you'd drink it!
いや、うーん。食後かな？食後！
Well, hmm. After a meal? After a meal!
我は...
Ware (I) am...
我？何でちょっと魔王っぽいの？
Ware? Why do you sound like a demon king?
食事時だなぁ！食事時！
During a meal! During a meal!
食事時と食後って言いました？これなんかここらへんが違うのでは？
Did you say during a meal and after a meal? Maybe this is where it's different?
食事中だぜ！
It's during a meal, daze!
もちろん食事中にも飲むな、飲むな。
Of course, I drink it during meals too.
いやでもね、ラミィもどっちかっていうと食後だぜ、これ。
But you know, for Lamy, it's more like after a meal, daze.
熱血！
Hot-blooded!
勢い飲んだぜ！
I drank with spirit, daze!
固まったな！
You froze!
これは、立ち位置変わらなくてもいいのでは？
Don't you think we don't even need to move positions for this?
勢い飲んだぜ！
I drank with spirit, daze!
そうなんだ。他に何か？
I see. Anything else?
ヘルシーな感じがあるんだぜ。
It has a healthy feel to it, daze.
確かにヘルシーな感じだぜ。でもヘルシーじゃないのもあるぜ。
It certainly feels healthy, daze. But there's also a non-healthy version, daze.
へっ？えっ？
Huh?
あ、あれ、そらちゃんこっちだぜ。ヘルシーじゃないバージョンもあるぜ。
Wait, Sora-chan is over here, daze. There's also a non-healthy version, daze.
これは...ない！ないぜ！
There... isn't one! There isn't one, daze!
あんまり思い浮かばないな！
I can't really think of any!
これは...これは...きっと...もしかして...
This is... this is... surely... maybe...
今自習移動するか。
Should we move positions now?
じゃあ多分、多分大丈夫なんだぜ。立ち位置は大丈夫なんだぜ。
Then maybe, maybe it's fine, daze. Our positions are fine, daze.
この立ち位置で。じゃあ、えーっと、終了ってことなんだぜ。
With these positions. Well then, it's over, daze.
みんな怪しい方を指すぜーの！
Everyone, point to the suspicious one, ready!
指すぜ！
Point!
まぁ、じゃあ、じゃあえーっと、吾輩から。吾輩が怪しいなと思ったのは...
Well, then, starting with me. The one I thought was suspicious is...
ラミィちゃんだぜ！
Lamy-chan, daze!
私も同じくラミィちゃんだぜ。
I also think it's Lamy-chan, daze.
同じくラミィちゃんだぜ。
Same here, it's Lamy-chan, daze.
ラミィちゃん、ヘルシーって言った、ヘルシーじゃないのはないって。思い浮かばないんだぜ、っていう。
Lamy-chan said it's healthy, but then said there isn't a non-healthy version. Like she couldn't think of any.
さぁ、それでは、みんなが何を飲んでいたのか。誰がウルフだったのか。発表だぜ！
Now then, let's reveal what everyone was drinking. Who was the wolf? Announcement, daze!
だぜ！
Daze!
ドン！
Don!
【 燦鳥ノム 】黒烏龍茶
【 ときのそら 】黒烏龍茶
【 雪花ラミィ 】クラフトボス ブラック
[ Suntory Nomu ] Black Oolong Tea
[ Tokino Sora ] Black Oolong Tea
[ Yukihana Lamy ] Craft Boss Black
確かにこれは黒烏龍茶にヘルシーじゃないのはないですね。
Indeed, for Black Oolong Tea, there isn't a non-healthy version.
あ、他にも...
Ah, others too...
あ～他にもいろいろ...
Ah, there were various others...
あ～、やっちまったぜ！
Ah, I blew it!
難しかったぜ！
That was hard!
美味しかった
It was delicious.
美味しかったぜ
いや～、そらちゃんが2勝なんだぜ！
Wow, Sora-chan won twice!
そうだぜ！やった～！
That's right! Yay!
おめでとう～！
Congratulations!
いいじゃないか！
Isn't it great!
なんか一緒に喜んじゃったけど
I kind of celebrated together with you guys.
いやいやいや、これは楽しいですね
No no no, this is fun.
ね～
Right?
というわけで、こうやってね、コメントもね、
So, like this, we're getting lots of comments,
たくさん来ておりますけれども、さすがそらちゃんと来てますね
like "as expected of Sora-chan".
やったー！
Yay!
流石！
Impressive!
いや、こうやってそらちゃんラミィちゃんと、お歌だけでなく、
Well, it's so much fun being able to play like this,
遊ぶことができてとっても楽しいですね
not just sing, with Sora-chan and Lamy-chan.
うん
Yeah.
ご覧の皆様、お楽しみ頂けましただぜ！
Everyone watching, I hope you enjoyed it!
まだそれ引きずってる感じですね
You're still dragging that out, huh?
楽しかったぜ！熱血！
It was fun! Hot-blooded!
熱血難しいですね
Hot-blooded is hard, isn't it?
ブレブレだったよ
I was all over the place.
ブレブレ...
All over the place...
「我」って言い始めましたもんね
You even started saying "ware".
「我、我」って、一人称がちょっと難しかったんだぜ
Saying "ware, ware", first-person pronouns were a bit tough.
そうだぜ！
That's right!
ね、たくさん「そらちゃんおめでとう」と
Right, lots of "Congratulations Sora-chan" messages.
ありがとうございます！
Thank you!
おめでとうございます
Congratulations.
はい。それでは次のコーナーに移りたいと思いますので、
Yes. Well then, we'd like to move on to the next corner,
一旦スタジオの準備をさせていただきます。
so we'll prepare the studio.
少々お待ちください
Please wait for a while.
ただいまセッティング中です しばらくお待ちください
Setting up now. Please wait a moment.
はい、たくさんのコメントありがとうございます！
Yes, thank you for all the comments!
続いてはこちらのコーナーに参りましょう
Next, let's move on to this corner.
アンケートト～ク！
Survey Talk!
今からトーク内容のお題が出てきますので、
Topics for the talk will appear now,
ご覧の皆様の投票でどんなお話をするか決めていきます
and we'll decide what to talk about based on your votes.
チャット欄にアンケートが出てまいりますので、
A survey will appear in the chat section,
皆様どんどん投票してください
so everyone please cast your votes.
それではトークテーマはこちらです！
Well then, here are the talk themes!
ジャジャーン！出ますでしょうか？
Tada! Will they appear?
じゃあ、「お勧めしたいもの」、
Okay, "Something I'd like to recommend",
「自分なりの決めポーズ」、
"My own signature pose",
「今年挑戦したい料理」、となります！
and "A dish I want to try cooking this year"!
はい、この3つ。「お勧めしたいもの」、
Yes, these three. "Something I'd like to recommend",
「自分なりの決めポーズ」、
"My own signature pose",
「今年挑戦したい料理」。
and "A dish I want to try cooking this year".
おお、それでは皆様、投票お願いいたします！
Oh, then everyone, please vote!
あ、準備の方はよろしいでしょうか？
Ah, is everyone ready?
ドキドキドキ。いや、どれが選ばれると思います？
Pounding heart. Well, which one do you think will be chosen?
「自分なりの決めポーズ」っていうのが凄い気になるんですけど
I'm really curious about "My own signature pose".
おお、「自分なりの」。
Oh, "my own".
自分が一番「あ、これ最高でしょう」みたいなポーズ。え～
Like the pose you think is best. Wow.
これが最高、って今やっちゃって...
This is the best... oh you're doing it now...
今やっちゃった。後でもう一回やらなきゃいけないですね
I just did it. I'll have to do it again later.
はい。じゃあアンケート開始です。
Yes. Now, the survey starts.
皆様、投票お願いいたします
Everyone, please vote.
みんなはどれが聞きたいんだろうね。どれなんでしょう
I wonder which one everyone wants to hear. Which one could it be?
どれなんでしょう
Which one could it be?
「今年挑戦したい料理」、
"A dish I want to try cooking this year",
「二人にお勧めしたいもの」。
"Something I'd like to recommend to the two of you".
え～、どんなのだろうな。皆様どうですか？
Hmm, I wonder what they are. What do you all think?
「決めポーズ」面白そうってきてますね
Someone says "Signature pose" looks interesting.
いや、これは気になる。気になりますね。
No, I'm curious. Very curious.
二人の決めポーズが気になる！
I'm curious about your signature poses!
えっ、それを、それを考えるアンケートなんだ、振る、作る、今ちょっとお時間...
Wait, this survey is to think about that, to perform, to create,
今ちょっとお時間...
wait, give me a moment...
今、今考えときますね、今
I'll think of it now, right now.
えっと考えましょう。ちょっとじゃあ繋いでて...
Let's think. For a bit, keep things going...
みんな、どうかな、何が...
Everyone, what do you think? What...
あ、どうしよう「決めポーズ」、じゃあちょっと二人の決めポーズ、
Oh no, "signature pose", well, if it becomes "signature pose",
もし「決めポーズ」になったらノムちゃんにやってもらいましょうよ
let's have Nomu-chan do your signature poses.
あ、なるほどね。二人の決めポーズを
Ah, I see. Your signature poses.
確かに。さあ...
Indeed. Well then...
終了です！
Finished!
終了！
それでは結果を見てみましょう。どうぞ！
Then let's look at the results. Here you go!
えっと、自分なりのキメポーズですね！
Um, our own signature poses!
キメポーズ！
Signature pose!
うーん、キメポーズ。じゃ、どなたから行きますか？
Yeah, signature pose. Well, who wants to go first?
自信満々のラミィちゃん？
Lamy-chan, who's full of confidence?
自信満々だったの？初めて聞いたよ、自信満々だったって。
I was full of confidence? First time I've heard that.
ええ、自信全然なかったです。
Eh, I wasn't confident at all.
ノムさんにやってもらいますかね？
Should Nomu-san show us?
きっとすごく可愛いんでしょうね、皆さん。
I'm sure it'll be very cute, everyone.
じゃ、やっぱりね、可愛いポーズやりましょうか。
Well, after all, let's do a cute pose.
あ、楽しみですわ。
Oh, I'm looking forward to it.
じゃちょっとラミィのこの、今日のサムネイルにもなっているポーズ、こちら！
Well, let's see Lamy's pose that's also in today's thumbnail, this one!
これがラミィのキメポーズ！
This is Lamy's signature pose!
可愛らしい！
Lovely!
これですか。あ、いいですね！
This is the one. Oh, it's good!
いいね！そらちゃんもぜひ。
It's good! Sora-chan, you too please.
はい！いいですね！
Yes! It's good!
それで素晴らしい！
That's wonderful!
あ、ありがとうございます、考えていただいて。
Ah, thank you for thinking about it.
で、ああ、やっぱりお一人ずつやっていく感じですね。
And, ah, it seems like we're doing them one by one.
どうします？そらちゃん先行きます？
What should we do? Sora-chan, do you want to go first?
私のキメポーズというか今日のやつは、サムネイル...
My signature pose, or rather today's one, the thumbnail...
...こんな感じになっていると...
...is something like this...
難しいと思う。
I think it's difficult.
よいしょ！これは体幹が必要ですわね。
Heave-ho! This requires core strength, doesn't it.
あ、いいですね！
Oh, it's good!
あとはこう前にやっちゃってるポーズもあるかな。
Maybe there's a pose where I'm leaning forward like this too.
あ、大丈夫？
Ah, are you okay?
こんな感じで。
Like this.
うーん、なるほど。
Hmm, I see.
すごいバランス取ってる。
She's balancing so well.
え、ちょっと頭の中で次を考えてもらって...
Um, please think about the next one in your head...
じゃ行きましょうかね、ノムさんのキメポーズ。
Well, shall we go? Nomu-san's signature pose.
じゃわたくしは...これです！
Well, as for me... it's this!
えええ！これ！
Eee! This!
え？かっこいい顔で！はっ！
Eh? With a cool face! Ha!
これ何者のポーズ？
What kind of pose is this?
これは何でしょうね。
I wonder what this is.
さ、じゃで、ああ、せっかくなんでお二人で...
Right, well, since we're here, with the two of you...
じゃせーので行きましょうか。
Well, let's go on the count of three.
ぜーぜーぜーせーの！
Ready, go!
え、何をやる？
Eh, what are we doing?
え、わたくしの...わたくしの。
Eh, my... mine.
え、ノムちゃん...ノムちゃんのキメポーズお二人で決めるってことじゃないの？
Eh, Nomu-chan... isn't it that the two of us decide Nomu-chan's signature pose?
ちょっと説明させてください。
Please let me explain.
せーのの声なのノムさんのキメポーズがひどいので...
The "ready, go" was because Nomu-san's signature pose is terrible...
...お二人で考えてあげてくださいってラミィさんが。
...so please think of one for me, as Lamy-san said.
なるほどなるほど。
I see, I see.
ちょっとひどいって言わないでくださいって。
Wait, don't say it's terrible.
私もそういう意味かと思って。
I thought that's what it meant too.
ノムちゃんに合いそうだなとは今やってた。
I was just doing what seemed to suit Nomu-chan.
Okayです。じゃお二人でせーのでやって...
Okay. Well, the two of you do it together...
...その二つをやってもらいましょうか。
...and let me do those two.
二つもやってもらうの？かしこまりました。
Doing two? Understood.
じゃせーので行きましょうか。
Well, shall we go together?
せーの！
Ready, go!
位置でも変われば...そらちゃんが...足がこうで...
Even if the position changes... Sora-chan's... leg is like this...
...ああ、エレガントですわね。
...ah, it's elegant.
あ、ラミィちゃんは可愛いですね、こうで。
Ah, Lamy-chan is cute, like this.
フラフラしちゃう。ノムさんフラフラしちゃう。
I'm wobbling. Nomu-san is wobbling.
なるほど。ノム...何がいけないんですか？
I see. What is wrong with it?
かっこいいと思うよ。
I think it's cool.
そうですわね。足の角度もありますしね、無理のない。
That's right. There's also the leg angle, it's effortless.
そうですわ。あの皆さんも、リスナーの皆さんもやってくださいね。
That's right. Um, everyone, listeners, please do it too.
一緒にやるの？
We do it together?
お写真撮る際はこちらで。
When taking photos, use this.
え、これですか？
Eh, this one?
じゃもう一問アンケート行きましょうか。
Well, let's do another poll question.
今のこのポーズを抜いた残りの二つですね。
The remaining two, excluding this pose.
なるほど。
I see.
おすすめしたいもの、こと、もしくは今年挑戦したい料理。
Things/events to recommend, or dishes to challenge this year.
それでは皆さん投票お願いいたします。
Well then, everyone, please vote.
やー！
Yah!
おすすめ...まだ決定してないですね。
Recommendation... it hasn't been decided yet.
ね、おすすめしたいもの、こと。結構範囲が広いね。
Right, things/events to recommend. The range is quite wide.
お、でも結構割れてますね。真ん中、半分半分ぐらい。
Oh, but it's quite split. In the middle, about half and half.
ね、皆さん何が知りたいんでしょうね。気になる。
Right, I wonder what everyone wants to know. I'm curious.
お料理じゃないですか？今年挑戦したい料理。
Isn't it the dishes? Dishes to challenge this year.
わたくしたちね。料理しますか？
Us, then. Do you cook?
あまり...ノムさんします？
Not much... do you cook, Nomu-san?
わたくしは全くしないんですけれども。
I don't do it at all, but...
もしこれに答えることになったら...
If I end up answering this...
ビーフストロガノフって言おうと思います。
I think I'll say Beef Stroganoff.
アンケート実施中！！チャット欄から投票してください！！
Survey in progress!! Please vote in the chat!!
はい、答えはこちらです！
Yes, here is the answer!
はい！
Yes!
おすすめ...だ... 今の「&」のところ...
Recommended... the... that "&" part just now...
今、今年挑戦したい料理、聞きましたからね、今。
I just heard about the dishes you want to try this year.
何でも言っておけば大丈夫ですわ。挑戦したいですから。
Anything is fine to say. Since it's something you want to try.
なるほど、得意料理ではないので。
I see, it's not a specialty dish.
しかも満場一致で、じゃあビーフストロガノフ...
ただ、今おすすめしたいことですから。
And unanimously, then beef stroganoff...
But, this is about what I want to recommend now.
そうですよね！
That's right!
料理じゃないんだ... 残念ですわ...
It's not cooking... Too bad...
えー、何にしましょう。おすすめしたい... うーん。
Hmm, what should it be? What I want to recommend... Hmm.
物でも事でもいいみたいですね。
Seems like it can be a thing or an action.
ええ、物でも事でもいい。うーん。
Yes, a thing or an action is fine. Hmm.
あ、じゃあ私、最近、あの、購入して良かったものがあって。
Oh, then I have something I recently bought and liked.
おお！何だろう。
Oh! What is it?
あの、シルクのナイトキャップ。
Um, a silk nightcap.
へえー！
Heh~!
寝るときに被るんです。そうすると、あの、枕との摩擦が、その、なくなるので...
You wear it when you sleep. By doing so, um, the friction with the pillow disappears, so...
髪の毛が傷みにくいと。
The hair becomes less likely to get damaged.
素晴らしい！
Wonderful!
それを今日、えっと、2つセットで...
And today, um, as a set of two...
えっ、何より？
Eh, what for?
えっ、買わされるんですか？
Eh, are we being made to buy them?
ブブッ、ブブッ。正解、準備できてませんでしたわ。
Bzzzt, bzzzt. Correct answer, I wasn't prepared.
そうなんです。シルク、ナイトキャップ。シルクのナイトキャップが...
That's right. Silk, nightcap. A silk nightcap is...
被ったことないです。
I've never worn one.
結構おすすめです。ラミちゃん、お髪もきれいなので。
I highly recommend it. Lamy-chan's hair is beautiful too.
おお、ありがとうございます。
Oh, thank you very much.
ね、くるくると巻いて入れていただいて。そうなんです、おすすめですわ。
Right, you just curl it up and put it in. Yes, I recommend it.
ほら、皆さん使ってるよ、使ってるよ。
Look, everyone's using it, using it.
書いてないですね。
They haven't written that.
使ってるよ、そんなに見つめないでくださいまし！
They are using it, please don't stare at me like that!
持ってる、持ってる。
They have it, they have it.
一人もいなかったですね、今のは。
There wasn't even one person just now.
持ってる、持ってるって。
They're saying "I have it, I have it."
ノムちゃんにはそう見えていたんだね。
That's how it looked to Nom-chan, I guess.
私には幻、幻なんです、それは。
To me it's a phantom, a phantom, that is.
残念ですが... 残念ですが。
It's unfortunate... It's unfortunate.
他に何かおすすめ...
Anything else recommended...
え、ラミは最近、やってるのが、朝起きたら白湯を飲む。
Um, what Lamy has been doing lately is drinking hot water when I wake up in the morning.
ああ、いいですねー！
Ah, that's good!
なんか、すごく、こう、喉が最近乾燥するので。
Like, my throat has been getting really dry lately.
朝起きてこうお水を飲みたいんだけど、こう冷えたもの飲んじゃうと体が...
I want to drink water when I wake up, but if I drink something cold, my body...
そうですね、体温が下がりますわ。
That's right, your body temperature will drop.
だから、朝起きたらこう白湯を一杯飲むと、すごい、こう頭も切れるし。
So, drinking a cup of hot water when you wake up, it really clears your head.
喉も潤うし、すごいおすすめですよ。
It also hydrates the throat, I highly recommend it.
いいことしかないですわね。
There's only good things about it.
ほら、みんな飲んでるよ、飲んでるよ。
Look, everyone's drinking it, drinking it.
書いてないですね。ええ、コメ欄、やめてください。
They haven't written that. Please stop, comment section.
あ、でもほら、白湯いいよ、ってありますわ。
Ah, but look, there's "hot water is good."
ああ、ね。体にいいよね。
Ah, yeah. It's good for the body, right.
そら先輩は、何かありますか？
Sora-senpai, do you have anything?
えっと、私は、えっと、たまになんですけど。
Um, I, um, it's only once in a while.
毎日やると、すごい筋肉痛になっちゃうので。
If I do it every day, I get really sore muscles.
あんまり毎日ではないんだけど、体幹を鍛えるための...
It's not exactly every day, but for strengthening the core...
こう、ポーズみたいなのがあって。
Like, there's this pose.
おお！ポーズ。
Oh! A pose.
でも、できるかな。寝転がらなきゃいけないから。
But, I wonder if I can. Because I have to lie down.
えっ、ちょっと。ちょっと見れるかどうか分からないんですけど。
Eh, wait. We're not sure if we can see it.
こう、こういう。あ、やってみます、じゃあ。えっと。
Like, this. Oh, I'll try it then. Um.
こう、こうなって。で。
Like, like this. And then.
おおー。
Ohh.
ここ、あ、腕、つけた後に、グッて。
After, ah, putting your arms down, push up.
うわー！すごい！
Woa~! Amazing!
このポーズで、あのね、1分以上キープするっていうのを...
Holding this pose for, you know, over a minute...
1分！
One minute!
やると、結構ね、それだけで体幹、インナーマッスルとかが鍛えられて。
When you do it, you know, the core and inner muscles get strengthened quite a bit by just that.
結構いい感じ。
It's quite nice.
これ、え、ノムちゃん、行きましょうよ。
This, eh, Nom-chan, let's go.
天の声なんて無視でいいんですわ！
You can just ignore the voice from heaven!
でも、そんなに。天の声なんていいですけど、やりますか。
But, even so. The voice from heaven is fine, but shall we do it?
ああ、二人ともやりましょう。二人でやりましょう。
Ah, let's both do it. Let's do it together.
二人ともやりましょうと、天の声があったので。なるほど。
Since there was a voice from heaven saying "let's both do it." I see.
えっと、こうして、浮かせ、ハイ！
Um, like this, and lift up, there!
せーの！
Ready, go!
で、これをずっと1分間キープするっていうのを...
And then, keeping this for a whole minute...
1分！
One minute!
3回ぐらいセットでやる。
Do it in about 3 sets.
まだ歌うんです、ちょっと。
We still have to sing, wait.
まだ歌うから、はあー、皆さんご機嫌よう。
Because we still have to sing, whew, good day to you all.
結構でも、慣れてくるとセットでできる...
But quite, once you get used to it, you can do sets...
待って、まだ歌うの。
Wait, we're still singing.
まだ体力を残しておかないと。
We have to save some physical strength.
ありがとうございます。こういうのは、あの、毎日やってると、あの, 腹筋とかが鍛えられて。
Thank you very much. Things like this, if you do them every day, your abs and such get strengthened.
こう、こういうポーズやってるときに体幹が鍛えられて...
Like, while doing this kind of pose, your core gets strengthened...
わー、さっきのポーズにつながる。さすがそら先輩！
Wow, it leads to the pose from earlier. As expected of Sora-senpai!
なるほど、ねえ。
I see, right.
楽しい放送でしたわね。
It was a fun broadcast, wasn't it.
えっ、とても楽しい放送...
Eh, a very fun broadcast...
まだ残ってますから。まだでしたわね。
We still have more left. Not yet, right.
いや、大変でしたけれども。
No, it was tough, but.
プランク、プランクですわね。
Plank, it's the plank, isn't it.
頑張りましたわね。
We did our best, didn't we.
いや、皆さんのいろんな話...
No, everyone's various stories...
次、1曲歌っ...
Next, sing one song...
…も疲れてるじゃないですか。
...aren't you tired too?
ああ、そうそうそう。
Ah, yeah, yeah.
いろんなお話を聞くことができました。
I was able to hear many different stories.
はい。もっとお喋りしたいところでございますが、
Yes. I'd like to chat more, but...
ここからいよいよライブ後半です！
...from here, it's finally the second half of the live!
最後まで…歌えますでしょうか？
Until the end... can I sing?
この状況で。
In this situation.
大丈夫大丈夫！
It's okay, it's okay!
ね！
Right!
はい、最後までぜひお楽しみください。
Yes, please enjoy until the end.
えっと、ステージとマイクのセッティングに
Um, the stage and microphone setup
少々お時間いただきますので、
will take a little while, so...
皆さん、もう少々お待ちください。
...everyone, please wait a little longer.
頑張りまーす！
We'll do our best!
ただいまセッティング中です しばらくお待ちください
Currently setting up. Please wait for a while.
水の色
The color of water
誰もが同じ
Everyone is the same
空の色
The color of the sky
全て繋がる
Everything is connected
夕焼け
Sunset
また明日
See you tomorrow
これからも一緒に遊びましょうね
Let's keep playing together
どこまでも
Forever and ever
見上げて 空から
Looking up, from the sky
青が降り注ぐ
Blue pours down
繋がりは青
The connection is blue
揺るがない答え
An unwavering answer
これは始まりの物語
This is the beginning of the story
涙は海になる
Tears become the sea
絆は消えない
The bond will never fade
いつまでも
Forever
よろしくね
I'm glad to be with you
虹色
Rainbow colors
ここがステージ
Here is the stage
鳥は鳴き
Birds chirp
私は歌う
And I sing
水面
The water surface
跳ねる音
The sound of splashing
これからもみんなで見つけましょうね
Let's all find it together from now on
どこまでも
Forever and ever
探して 見つけて
Searching and finding me
くれてありがとう
Thank you for doing that
空と海青
Sky and sea blue
全て繋がってる
Everything is connected
これは終わらない物語
This is a never-ending story
笑顔が空になる
Smiles become the sky
絆は消えない
The bond will never fade
いつまでも
Forever
よろしくね
I'm glad to be with you
歩み続けた日々 愛しくて
The days I kept walking are dear
みんなと夢叶えていきたくて
I want to make dreams come true with everyone
新しい思い出をもっと
More new memories
見上げて 空から
Looking up, from the sky
青が降り注ぐ
Blue pours down
繋がりは青
The connection is blue
揺るがない答え
An unwavering answer
これは始まりの物語
This is the beginning of the story
光が溢れ出す
Light begins to overflow
絆は消えない
The bond will never fade
どこまでも
Forever
紡ぐ 新たな未来
Spinning a new future
思いを繋げてく
Connecting our feelings...
歌になる
It becomes a song.
夢の数だけ夢は
Dreams grow bigger
大きくなるんだって
for every dream you have,
小さな頃から
I should have known that
知ってたはず
since I was little.
心が折れかけて
Even if my heart starts to break
立ち止まってしまっても
and I come to a standstill,
ゴールは逃げたりしないから
the goal will never run away.
Step by Step ゆっくりでも
Step by step, even if it's slow,
一歩ずつ前だけ見て
look ahead one step at a time.
辛くても絶対に諦めない
No matter how hard it is, I'll never give up.
だって大切な仲間が
Because my precious friends
いつも側にいるから
are always by my side.
行くよ！明日への境界線を
Here I go! I want us all to jump over
みんなでせーの飛び越えたい
the boundary to tomorrow together.
繋がる絆は離れない
The bond that connects us will never break.
ずっと 空回りが空回し
Always, even if I'm just spinning my wheels
つまずくこともあるけど
and stumbling sometimes,
平気、大丈夫
it's okay, I'll be fine.
そう仲間を信じて進め
Yes, believe in your friends and move forward.
絆が深まるほど
As the bond deepens,
夢は確信に変わる
the dream turns into a conviction.
素敵な未来を描こうね
Let's paint a wonderful future together.
一歩ずつ怖がらずに
One step at a time, without fear,
声合わせて空見上げて
let's raise our voices and look up at the sky.
暗闇もいつかは晴れるからね
Even the darkness will clear up someday.
道に迷って落ち込む私を
When I lose my way and feel down,
照らしてくれる
you light the way for me.
行くよ！夢との境界線へ
Here I go! Let's all jump into
みんなでせーの飛び込もう
the boundary of our dreams together.
思いを繋げて未来まで
Let's connect our feelings until the future.
ずっと 遠回りが風吹かし
Always, even if the detour is windy
倒れることもあるけど
and I fall down sometimes,
ずっと、一緒だよ
we'll always be together.
さあ描いた夢まで進め
Now, move forward to the dream you've envisioned.
みんな、この曲はChu-Chu-Luっていう曲だよ！
Everyone, this song is called 'Chu-Chu-Lu'!
手拍子とかコメントとか、たくさん一緒に楽しんでくれるととっても嬉しいです！
I'd be so happy if you enjoy it with lots of clapping and comments!
男の子はいつでも
Boys are always
強がりな生き物
creatures that act tough.
弱さを嫌って
They hate weakness
涙は流さないの
and don't shed tears.
傷つかない人など
There's no one
この世にいないから
who doesn't get hurt in this world.
たまには本当の
So, occasionally,
声を聞かせてよ
let me hear your true voice.
あなたはまだ不器用なウルフ
You're still a clumsy wolf.
もういいよ 牙なんて捨てて
It's okay now, just throw away your fangs.
深く深く愛してよ
Love me deeply, deeply.
酸いも甘いもメモリアル
A memorial of both bittersweet moments.
恋は怖くないんだよ
Love isn't something to be afraid of.
あなたなら大丈夫
If it's you, you'll be fine.
強く強くハグしてよ
Hold me tightly, tightly.
あの夜にサヨナラを
Say goodbye to that night.
いつもここで待ってるよ
I'm always waiting here for you.
だからもっと
So, even more,
恐れずに
without fear,
愛してね
please love me.
せーの！
One, two!
チュルチュチュ チュルチュチュ
Chu-ru-chu-chu, chu-ru-chu-chu
誰もがひとりだけじゃ
No one can
いられない生き物
live all alone.
弱さを認め合い
Let's acknowledge each other's weaknesses
助け合うものよ
and help each other.
あたしもまだ不器用なエンジェル
I'm still a clumsy angel too.
お願いよ 翼を広げて
I'm begging you, spread your wings.
高く高く飛んでいくよ
We'll fly high, high up.
目指すのはサンクチュアリ
Our goal is the sanctuary.
二人だけの楽園で
In a paradise just for the two of us,
甘い果実かじり
let's bite into sweet fruits.
手と手ギュッと繋いでよ
Hold my hand tightly.
じゃなきゃ離れちゃうから
Otherwise, we might drift apart.
ずっとここで一緒だよ
We'll always be together here.
だからもっと
So, even more,
いつまでも
forever,
愛してね
please love me.
いつかできた傷跡に
If tears soak into the scars
涙が沁みちゃうのなら
that were made someday,
笑顔のバンドエイドを
I'll give you
あげるから
a Band-Aid of smiles.
前を向いてさ
Look forward
行こう
and let's go.
深く深く愛してよ
Love me deeply, deeply.
何もかもがメモリアル
Everything is a memorial.
恋は怖くないでしょう
Love isn't scary, is it?
あなたとあたしなら
If it's you and me.
強く強くハグしてよ
Hold me tightly, tightly.
あの夜にサヨナラを
Say goodbye to that night.
いつもここで待ってるよ
I'm always waiting here for you.
だからもっと
So, even more,
恐れずに
without fear,
愛してね
please love me.
チュルチュチュ チュルチュチュ
Chu-ru-chu-chu, chu-ru-chu-chu
ただいまセッティング中です　しばらくお待ちください
Setting up now. Please wait for a while.
ただいまセッティング中です しばらくお待ちください
Currently setting up. Please wait a moment.
皆さん、いかがでしたか？ 楽しんでいただけましたでしょうか？
How was it, everyone? Did you enjoy it?
はい。えー、ではちょっとクラフトボスティーの無糖を飲みながら、
Yes. Well, I'd like to take a look at everyone's comments
皆様のコメントを、あの、拝見したいなと思います。
while drinking some unsweetened Craft Boss Tea.
あ、どーせですので、あの、本日の放送祝して最後にもう一度乾杯をしておきましょう！
Ah, since we're here, let's have one last toast to celebrate today's broadcast!
やったー！
Yay!
せーの、乾杯！
One, two, cheers!
ぷはー。
Phew.
美味しい！
Delicious!
美味しいです！
It's delicious!
ねえ、今度は皆さんと同じ飲み物で。
Right, this time with the same drink as everyone.
おやつですわね。誰か止まってるとかないですよね？ 大丈夫ですわね。
It's snack time. Is anyone frozen? No, we're fine.
ねえ。あの、見てくださってる方も一緒に水分補給してください。
Yes. Everyone watching, please make sure to stay hydrated too.
ねえ、コメント見てみましょうか。
Right, shall we look at the comments?
お、オリジナル曲パート最高でした！
Oh, "The original song part was the best!"
嬉しい！
Happy!
ありがとう！ ありがとうございます！
Thank you! Thank you very much!
あ、ね、乾杯もありがとうございます。
Ah, yes, thank you for the toast too.
乾杯！
Cheers!
嬉しいですね。たくさんありがとうございます。
It makes me happy. Thank you so much for everything.
うんうん。ああ、本当だ。たくさん見てるね。ありがとうございます。
Yeah, yeah. Oh, it's true. So many people are watching. Thank you.
あ、3人ともお疲れ様でしたって。ありがとう！
Ah, "Good job to the three of you." Thank you!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
プランクが効きましたわね。
The prank really worked, didn't it?
なかなかね、もう焦りました。え、ここで来ると思って。
It really did, I was so flustered. I didn't think it would come then.
ごめんなさい！
I'm sorry!
なんとか、なんとか乗り切れましたね。
We managed, we managed to get through it.
続けていきたいなと思いましたわ。うん。
I thought I wanted to keep going. Yeah.
嬉しいです。ありがとうございます。
I'm happy. Thank you very much.
あの、本日改めて今日は、あの、ありがとうございました。
Um, once again, thank you for today.
え、ライブは久しぶりでは、あの、あったんですけれども、
It's been a while since my last live, but I hope I was able to
最高の時間を皆様にお届けできたかなと思っております。
bring you all a wonderful time.
え、では最後に、なりますが、そらちゃん、ラミィちゃん、本日の放送はいかがでしたでしょうか？ そらちゃん。
Well, it's coming to an end, but Sora-chan, Lamy-chan, how was today's broadcast for you? Sora-chan.
はい。いやもうなんか、ちょっと久しぶりのライブだったので緊張してたんですけど、
Yes. Well, it was my first live in a while, so I was a bit nervous,
3人ですごくね、あの、わちゃわちゃとお話もできたし、
but we were able to have a lot of lively chat and perform
ライブもできたし、もう最高の時間だったなと思います。
the live together, so I think it was a wonderful time.
美味しい飲み物もいっぱいもらっちゃって、もう言うことないです！
I also got lots of delicious drinks, so I have nothing more to say!
皆さん見てくれてありがとうございました。
Everyone, thank you for watching.
そしてゲストに呼んでいただいてありがとうございました！ とっても楽しかったです！
And thank you for having me as a guest! I had so much fun!
ありがとうございました、そらちゃん。
Thank you very much, Sora-chan.
それではラミィちゃん、本日の放送いかがでしたでしょうか？
Now Lamy-chan, how was today's broadcast for you?
もう今日は、本当に面白かったです！
It was really interesting today!
なんかね、もうノムちゃんが初めてだったんですけど、
Well, it was my first time meeting Nomu-chan,
すごい面白くて、あっという間に時間が過ぎちゃったのもあるし、
but she's so funny, and time just flew by,
そら先輩とね、こうして一緒に、そら先輩とノムちゃんと
and being able to sing on the same stage like this with
同じステージでね、歌ったりできるのが本当に夢みたいで楽しかったです。ありがとうございました。
Sora-senpai and Nomu-chan was really like a dream and so much fun. Thank you very much.
ありがとうございました。いや、私も本日こう、そらちゃんとラミィちゃんとご一緒できて嬉しかったです。
Thank you very much. No, I was also happy to be with Sora-chan and Lamy-chan today.
こう3人の並びがまた統一感があって、本当に本日のウィンターライブにぴったりだったなと思いますし、
The three of us lined up like this has a sense of unity, and I think it was perfect for today's winter live,
こうワードウルフで、ね、お互いをちょっと疑い合ったりもしましたし。
and we even suspected each other a bit during Word Wolf.
あの、本当に最後のトーク、テーマのトークも楽しくお話ができて、
Um, the final talk about the theme was also fun,
本当にお二方のことをより知ることができて嬉しかったです。
and I'm happy I could get to know the two of you better.
はい、皆様も遊びに来てくださって本当にありがとうございました。
Yes, thank you all so much for coming to visit us too.
そして、あの、今日せっかくこうして3人が集まりましたので、
And, um, since the three of us have gathered together like this today,
最後にこう3人で一曲、はい、3人で一曲お歌を歌って、
let's finish with one song together, yes, let's sing a song
あの、皆様とお別れをさせていただきましょうか！
as a trio to say goodbye to everyone!
イェーイ！
Yay!
ねえ、コメント、あ、またやってほしい、ありがとうございます。ねえ、ぴったり、この色ぴったり、ありがとうございます。
Right, the comments... "Please do it again," thank you. "Perfect, these colors are perfect," thank you.
ありがとう！ たくさんコメントいただいて、ねえ、楽しかったよ、と、ありがとうございます。
Thank you! We received so many comments. "It was fun," thank you.
さあ、あ、じゃあ、あの、曲に移る前に、そらちゃんとラミィちゃんに
Now, ah, well, before we move on to the song, if Sora-chan
皆様にお伝えする告知などありましたら、お願いします。じゃあそらちゃんからいきましょうか。
or Lamy-chan have any announcements for everyone, please go ahead. Let's start with Sora-chan.
はい！ え、私はですね、5月15日のお誕生日に合わせて、
Yes! Well, for my birthday on May 15th,
え、ビクターエンタテインメントさんからシングルを出すんですけども、
I'll be releasing a single from Victor Entertainment,
そのシングルの、え、受注販売が今始まっております！
and pre-orders for that single have just started!
ぜひぜひ、猫をテーマにした曲を、え、作って皆さんに...
By all means, it's a song themed after cats, and I made it for everyone...
プレゼントだと思っているので、ぜひ見ていただけたらとっても嬉しいです！
I consider it a gift, so I'd be very happy if you'd take a look!
そして、こ、今日、こって言っちゃったｗ
And... t-today... I accidentally said "t-t" lol
今日見てくださった皆さん、本当にありがとうございます！
To everyone who watched today, thank you so much!
みんなのコメントもとっても楽しそうで、見てる私がとってもね、ウキウキになりました。
Everyone's comments looked so fun, it made me feel so excited just watching them.
もう終わっちゃうのは寂しいですが...
It's sad that it's already ending, but...
最後まで全力で盛り上げたいと思うので...
I want to keep the excitement going with all my heart until the very end, so...
今日は本当に、本当に最後まで楽しんでいってください！
Please enjoy yourselves until the very, very end today!
今日、ありがとうございました！
Thank you for today!
あー、ありがとうー！
Ah, thank you!
ありがとう！じゃあラミィちゃん、お願いします！
Thank you! Well then, Lamy-chan, if you please!
はい！それでは、3月19日、20日の間...
Yes! Well then, between March 19th and 20th...
幕張メッセ国際展示場で、ホロライブプロダクション最大級のイベント...
at Makuhari Messe International Exhibition Hall, Hololive Production's largest-ever event...
『hololive SUPER EXPO 2022 Supported By ヴァイスシュヴァルツ』を開催します！
"hololive SUPER EXPO 2022 Supported By Weiß Schwarz" will be held!
ホロライブの世界観が体感できる数々のブースもご用意しております。
We'll have many booths where you can experience the world of Hololive.
また、同期間、幕張メッセのイベントホールで、音楽ライブ...
Also, during the same period at the Makuhari Messe Event Hall, a music live...
『hololive 3rd fes. Link Your Wish Supported By ヴァイスシュヴァルツ』も開催しますので、ぜひぜひチェックしてみてください！
"hololive 3rd fes. Link Your Wish Supported By Weiß Schwarz" will also be held, so please check it out!
え、私と、ラミィと、そら先輩も、もちろん！はい、サードフェスに出演します！
Um, me, Lamy, and Sora-senpai will, of course, yes, be performing in the 3rd Fes!
公演に関するハッシュタグは共通で、#つながるホロライブ です。
The common hashtag for the performances is #LinkYourWish.
現地の来場チケットや、ライブの配信チケットなど詳細は、特設ホームページをチェックしてください！
Check the special website for details on venue tickets and live streaming tickets!
わー！ありがとうございます！楽しみですねー！
Wow! Thank you so much! We're looking forward to it!
ありがとうございますー。楽しみですー。ねー。
Thank you. We're looking forward to it, aren't we?
あ、私ですか？『藍色配信中』です。ぜひ聴いてください！
Oh, is it my turn? "Aoiro Haishin-chu" is out now. Please give it a listen!
聴くよー！いっぱい聴くよー！
We'll listen to it! We'll listen to it a lot!
いっぱい聴くよー！楽しみなお時間です、本当に。はい。
We'll listen to it a lot! It's such a fun time, really. Yes.
ありがとうございます。楽しみなお時間でした、本当に。はい。
Thank you. It was a really fun time. Yes.
本日は本当にご視聴いただきましてありがとうございました。
Thank you very much for watching today.
また皆様とこうしてお会いできることを楽しみにしております。
I look forward to meeting you all again like this.
それでは、燦鳥ノムPresents ウィンターminiライブ...
Now, for the Suntory Nom Presents Winter Mini Live...
本日最後の曲を聴いてください。
Please listen to the final song of today.
ときのそらと雪花ラミィと、燦鳥ノムで...
By Tokino Sora, Yukihana Lamy, and Suntory Nom...
せーの、スノーハレーション！
One, two, Snow halation!
不思議だね　今の気持ち
It's strange, the way I feel right now
空から降ってきたみたい
It's like it just fell from the sky
特別な季節の色が
The colors of this special season
ときめき見せるよ
Make my heart skip a beat
初めて出会った時から
From the moment we first met
予感に騒ぐ　心のメロディ
A melody stirs in my heart, a premonition
止められない　止まらない　何故
I can't stop it, it won't stop, why?
届けて　切なさには
Send it out, this bittersweet feeling
名前をつけようか
Shall we give it a name?
Snow halation
想いが重なるまで
Until our feelings overlap
待てずに悔しいけど　好きって純情
I can't wait, it's frustrating, but this love is pure
微熱の中　ためらってもダメだね
In this slight fever, hesitating won't do
飛び込む勇気に変えて　まもなくStart!!
Change it into the courage to dive in, soon it's Start!!
音もなく　気配もなく
Without a sound, without a sign
静かに運命は変わる
Destiny quietly changes
これからの未来に胸の
Regarding the future from now on
鼓動が早くなる
My heart beats faster
例えば困った時には
For instance, when you're in trouble
すぐ駆けつけて　抱きしめたくて
I want to rush over and hold you tight
どこにいても　どこまでも　Fly high
Wherever you are, to wherever, Fly high
急いで　いつの間にか
Hurry, before I knew it...
大きく過ぎたこのエモーション
This emotion that's grown too large
夢だけ見てるようじゃ
If it's just a dream
つらいよ
It's painful
恋人は君でいたい
I want you to be my lover
優しい目が戸惑ってるようだよ
Your gentle eyes seem bewildered
このまま一気に愛情
Just like this, all at once, my love...
預けて please
...entrust it to you, please
本日はご覧いただきましてありがとうございました！
Thank you so much for watching today!
とっても楽しかったよ！
It was so much fun!
最後はみんなで一緒に歌おうね！
Let's all sing together at the end!
みんな、行くよ！
Everyone, here we go!
届けて 切なさには
Deliver it, to this heartache
名前を付けようか
Shall we give it a name?
スノーハレーション
Snow halation
想いが重なるまで
Until our feelings overlap
待てずに悔しいけど
I can't wait, it's frustrating but...
好きって純情
...the feeling of "love" is pure.
微熱の中
Amidst a slight fever
ためらってもダメだね
Hesitating is no good, right?
飛び込む勇気にさせて
Give me the courage to dive in
まもなく start!!
It's about to start!!
番組は終了しました ご視聴ありがとうございました
The program has ended. Thank you for watching.